<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<article xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" article-type="research-article">
  <front>
    <journal-meta>
      <journal-id journal-id-type="nlm-ta">Hasya Katta Official</journal-id>
      <journal-id journal-id-type="publisher-id">HKO-001</journal-id>
      <journal-title>Hasya Katta Official</journal-title><issn pub-type="ppub">1</issn><issn pub-type="epub">1</issn><publisher>
      	<publisher-name>Hasya Katta Official</publisher-name>
      </publisher>
    </journal-meta>
    <article-meta>
      <article-id pub-id-type="doi">1</article-id>
      <article-categories>
        <subj-group subj-group-type="heading">
          <subject>Research Article</subject>
        </subj-group>
        <subj-group><subject>haysa katta official, hasya katta, smit shetye, shetye smit, prashik gawai, gawai prashik</subject></subj-group>
      </article-categories>
      <title-group>
        <article-title>Hasya Katta Official</article-title><subtitle>Hasya Katta Official</subtitle></title-group>
      <contrib-group><contrib contrib-type="author">
	<name name-style="western">
	<surname>Shetye</surname>
		<given-names>Smit</given-names>
	</name>
	<aff>Founder, CMD & CEO of Hasya Katta Official</aff>
	</contrib></contrib-group>		
      <pub-date pub-type="ppub">
        <month>10</month>
        <year>2020</year>
      </pub-date>
      <pub-date pub-type="epub">
        <day>2</day>
        <month>10</month>
        <year>2020</year>
      </pub-date>
      <volume>1</volume>
      <issue>1</issue>
      <permissions>
        <copyright-statement>© 2020 This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License, which permits unrestricted use, distribution, and reproduction in any medium, provided the original author and source are credited.</copyright-statement>
        <copyright-year>2020</copyright-year>
        <license license-type="open-access" xlink:href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/2.5/"><p>This is an open-access article distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution License, which permits unrestricted use, distribution, and reproduction in any medium, provided the original work is properly cited.</p></license>
      </permissions>
      <related-article related-article-type="companion" vol="2" page="e235" id="RA1" ext-link-type="pmc">
			<article-title>Hasya Katta Official</article-title>
      </related-article>
	  <abstract abstract-type="toc">
		<p>
			Tickle Your Funny Bone with All New MemesFeeling blue? Not anymore. All you need is a good laugh. And to bring just that to you, we’ve launched Hasya Katta! Hasya Katta Official is a Marathi social media page and app, bringing to you anecdotes, memes and much more. Comedy, satire, caricatures and good old memes, we have everything you’ll  need to laugh you guts out. Our content is in Marathi, but it’s open for everyone. The app comes with easy access social  media buttons, making it all the more easy for you to follow us! You can also check up on all our social media platforms  from this one app. No need to scroll aimlessly on many different apps! But that’s not it. Apart from watching tales and  laughing out loud at memes, you can even post your own content and get a chance to be featured on our page! Think you’re  up to the challenge? Let’s see your funny bone at work.The app is now available for android users, what are you waiting  , go and get it! We encourage you to not just laugh at our content, but also help spread the word about us! Follow us on  Instagram and other social media platforms. We welcome suggestions and original work! Our content is open for people to  use and share on social media, now go and share that funny meme with your friend. Spread the joy.
		</p>
		</abstract>
    </article-meta>
  </front>
  <body></body>
  <back>
    <ack>
      <p>We acknowledge the generous support of Parva Madhu, Sahil Joshi, Adnan Kazi, Aavesh Jilani</p>
    </ack>
  </back>
</article>
